We come back to the idea of ​​where the
cold in your
mind comes from.  And if you don't remember anything or
your friends ask: "Why
did you learn last
weekend?"  You must be prepared.  must
say yours.  I don't
remember.  This comrade said such and
such.  The voice in your mind is not
you.  And by the way, you have no choice what
this voice says.
If you are ever
depressed or you have broken up
with your girlfriend or
boyfriend, you cannot tell your mind
to stop telling me about it
.  Be comfortable with
it.  Be comfortable with this idea.
You don't control the person
who speaks in your mind.  But it is not
you, because those words were spoken
before you
heard them.  By the time you hear
these words, the one who spoke them has already left.
Where do these eyes
come from?  Onit from the seeds in your
mind.  And these seeds were planted
by you.  And no one else can
tell you what to think in your mind.
You can't say what's going on in your
mind.  If you have good ones in your
mind, this person who speaks in
your mind will be
incredible.  He will share new
ideas.  You will always be happy for the
rest of your lives.
If you don't learn to control this
process, it might end up the same as how
you came to this
Mexico referral.  Almost every person in this
world plants seeds
by accident.  They don't even know they are
planting seeds.
So these rens open up and they have
these thoughts in their
head and they have no
control throughout their entire
life.  It is not you
[the music]
speaking, and you have no choice in
hearing what your voice is
telling you now.
You have a choice next
week next week the voice
will be
incredible.  It's so cool to live in your head
when the one talking to you is
incredible.
Every week is better than the
last.  Don't you know how to
plant
names?  Then there is never-ending joy, a
joke.  And it keeps getting bigger and
bigger.  And that's a quarter of a billion
companies in Manhattan.
I got rid of it 25 years
ago.  It was just the beginning of
joy, much more joy after
that, because I know how to plant
seeds for the one who speaks in my mind.
And
he always tells me: “We would
love to do this.”  And I say, "
Maybe next year."
Maybe we'll fly past Mexico next year
[music]
.  What you learned this
weekend is how to plant these seeds.
I will repeat these
steps.  And then, if we have
extra
time, I'll give you a headache to
think about at
home.  And if we have
time left, we'll do a question and
answer session.  If you have questions,
have them ready.
We'll go look at the pictures because it's
much easier.  Remember these
steps.  I know that Pachi and Pau who are the big
bosstin.  This is their child.  This is the child of
Pacha and Pau.
I'm sure they will have follow-up
programs after this
retreat to explain all these
pictures again and
again.
So you use the same
pictures.  So, let
's begin.  Next
picture.  100
dollars.  Wait, I have
enough money.
Seriously?  Can we eat some more?  We
have money.
[music]
Yes.  So, 100
dollars.  What's going on in this
picture?  By the way, 50 dollars.  What's
going on in this picture?  55
dollars.  What is not happening in this
picture?
[music]
The woman in this picture has planted
seeds and they are growing into her like a
garden.
What does this tree
represent?  The seeds she
planted long ago have
grown.  This is the tree for her voice.
What was my other
question?  Grandpa asks, "What's not
happening in this picture?
She's not
eating. It's coming from it. She's not
eating that tree.
Great. I gave you a weird
picture because people remember
weird pictures.
They don't remember normal
pictures. When you think about it
this
weekend, just remember this
picture. I want to plant a
voice that comes into my
mind and tells me cool things
I can do.
How did I start a jewelry
company? Seven
dollars. But the person in my
mind is very, very...
In the diamond business, we have a
special
word. No, that doesn't mean
I had this voice in my mind.
Let's do the diamond business. The
diamond business. The
diamond business. Incredible. You
know, the biggest jewelry company
in the world.
If you break that
voice, so cool and fun.
[music]
How many pictures do you have? 10.
How do we get
home? Let's make it $100 each.
picture. Wait, wait.
Raise your hands. Don't raise your hands.
Now this picture
represents that you have many
choices, but the one
taught here is the best
choice. Go ahead, you choose.
Aldo. By the way, there's a special system.
He chooses you, but you give him
$50. No,
I have a special
system that will plant a
good one. Instead of what?
Instead of squandering
yours, you can squander many good
votes:
financial,
family happiness, good
health. You can choose several
votes, I think.
Creativity is one of the most important
voices. You can say, this is a new
idea
voice, because it is this voice that you
can use for all the
others. I have a new idea how
to create
money. I have a new idea how to
get my wife to cook and wash
the dishes.
or husband, get ready to wash the
dishes. I think, let's think about it. It
seems to me that my wife has already
done this. If you are very
creative, you will be able to be
creative in different areas of your life. And
in this lesson, in
this we are planting precisely the
creativity of that,  Who's talking in
your mind?
So, don't forget, each picture
is worth a hundred. If you're smart, raise
your hand now.
I'm kidding, I'm kidding. He said, "Next
picture."
Oh, go ahead and choose.
The music from Mission: Impossible. The
music from the movie Mission:
Impossible is not
good. Going to classes you
don't understand. Great. And I gave an
example of the funny nuts class.
I wasn't talking about all the classes, or
any
classes at all. Easy, easy advice. We
have two classes every
week. It's
free. These are translation classes.
They are very difficult.
These are difficult things that make you
stronger. Don't worry if you don't
understand everything, if you don't understand anything at all
, just come,
sit and
listen. Listen,
progress is in vain. It
doesn't go, it doesn't rise. That's how it
goes. That's how it goes. Look how it
shows you. And down, up, down, up,
down. You
go in, you will stop coming to these
classes for 3
weeks,  then you'll
come back. Same with meditation.
Meditate Netflix. Then watch
Netflix Netflix Netflix meditate,
meditate,
meditate then Netflix
Disney meditate,
meditate,
meditate. It's impossible to go up all the time
. Don't even think about it.
You're always going to do something wrong,
every month. So don't
worry. Chanting to keep from getting angry
. Patience, patience,
patience,
patience. Someone driving pushes you,
you
talk back, call them names. Again
patience, patience, patience, patience, patience, patience
,
patience. Not ideal.
If you're perfect, you shouldn't come
to this
class. It definitely means you'll
give up somewhere and do something
wrong. Don't be so
serious about it. Look at
Gishel's face. Oh, I forgot my meditation. Forgot my
meditation. Go tomorrow.
So, the next
picture. Oh, music with a movie is
impossible.
[music]
If you're under 21  years, you should invest
this money for your education in
collections. with
a lock where we put all our
gadgets at a certain
time, and this
helps you paradise your computers, iPads,
everything that you will do.
If you come to me when I
finish this
lesson, I will give you this small
suitcase, this handbag. I will
give it to you personally.
Cool.
[music]
It is a small handbag, and it
has a handle that you can even
wear on your shoulder. It is very, very
convenient. This is the most favorite thing in my
life.
If you forget to come to me, no
problem.
I will give it to you
. There is another one for Gesha Michael.
Yeah. Are you
ready? Next picture.
[music]
Before you
answer, this is related to the previous
picture.
No hands.
Next, in order to
experience what Deshela read from the
book Garden.
And this can happen to you if you
put away all the gadgets to have
time. This is a bad answer,  but it's a good
answer. It's the wrong answer, but it's a
good one. $100. But what does that
mean?
Before I started Good
Night
Club, by the way, I
stopped reading
printed books because they're so heavy to
carry around
. I put all the books down and download them to my
phone. But I still really like to
read before I go to bed.
If I read my phone before I
go to bed, I don't
sleep well. If I read a book that's
actually
printed, I sleep much
better. My advice to
you is from 10 a.m. to 6 a.m.
when I
travel and when I'm alone in a
hotel room, it's a very dangerous
place. I know I don't
trust myself. And I'll ask my friend, he
points to
Rob. At 10 o'clock he knocks on my
door, and I give him all my gadgets.
Okay. Take it,
take the computer. The computer. And the phone?
Then I say good
night. Come here. He shows
me the controls. Let's switch
TV in your
[laughter]
room. And I give it to him.
There are two TVs in my room.
Give
the second
[music]
strengthener. I don’t
know, if you do, change this
system, you will increase your productivity in the war
. How did
etoran?
What did he say?
You can buy something, eye makeup
or you can sleep 8
hours.
Personally, I think that a woman who sleeps
hours and uses a lot of
Sanran makeup, she does not look the same as
a woman who slept 8 hours.
8 hours is
natural. Your face becomes much
better,
rested. This is the heaviest
makeup. What is this place called?
Ah, Sephora.
Sephora. I’ll tell you something
interesting. She wants to go to Sephora.
He says to the men: “Find
any excuse not to go,
not to go
there.  Bring her to the
library.  The same lipstick
costs 2
dollars at the drugstore.  I'm telling you, it's
true."
So, it changes your face. It
makes your mind very
strong. You can make more than twice the
money. And you don't know because you've
never
done it. I'm not saying that one time
sleep at 8 o'clock.
If you do 3
weeks, your mind will become
stronger and you will feel, you will be
much
healthier. I'm
a grandfather, I come to
yoga classes, I do things where people are
20 years old. Everyone is like, "Wow!"
I just need to
sleep and put this stupid
phone away. Give them how many
hours? You have 16 hours to be on
your phone. But at 8
o'clock you can maybe be alone and
sleep.
And those 16 hours take up a lot of your
time. Please, please,
please, please
try it. If you don't have the strength to
do it, do it. He's on
Robocop. He bought a house next to my
house. He used to live a thousand miles from me. He
lives 2 minutes from
me when my wife is on vacation or
she's on her  I'm not
home, at 10 o'clock he knocks on my
door. He comes to my house and
shows me: "Give
me 10.
Find yourself a
friend, if you are like
me, if you don't have the willpower to do it
yourself, you need friends who
will do it for
you.  The phone is very similar to an
alcoholic.  We all depend on him.  All.
What is your favorite
phone?  Place to look at your phone.
I sit on this chair or in this corner
of my room to look at my
phone.  Afterwards, there is often a knock on my
door.  You know, I'm sitting in the toilet in
my place.  This is my favorite place.
Look at the
phone.  Sorry, no more
Trump news.  I haven't reviewed everything yet
.  Okay, be
careful.  Maybe you don't have the strength to
do it
yourself?  Find a friend who will do this for you
.  And help and help each
other.  You will never regret.
Never create a more successful
person, please.
Kentak Fri
Chicken.  I think that the company
kakki and Apple will simply
kill me.  And if you know why
something happened to me, now you know
why it happened.
[music]
When I travel, I
generally like to have a lot of
different books.  Sometimes I
feel like I can read something
deeper.  Or then I will
read the
Kamaz border.  Sometimes I feel very
tired.
So I
fall asleep or read something more
like a
book garden.  I advise you to have
two
books on your nightstand.  One is a little
deeper and the other is more relaxed.
With this, with this book, you will appreciate it, you will
appreciate it in 6
minutes.  Even if you read it in the morning
, you will fall asleep very
quickly.  Next
picture.  I didn't show this
picture.  I should have shown it, but I didn't
.
This is the last
picture in yesterday's
presentation.  I told you, there is a special
method.  Plant seeds to hear
your inner voice.  By the way, this
guy does it.
Alda chooses a person.
[music]
And the network, so that it is dark to think 24 hours
a day, when we look and talk,
we ask ourselves, what time did I plant,
what is happening to me, what did I
do to create this, everything that
Shala said in the last lesson, and he
answered correctly and received the money.
This activity, these 2 days, it’s so fun and
cool.
Why did
n't you
teach anything?  Onshala told me and did not teach you
new meditation, when he said, if
you do not do this, it will be even
worse for you.  Likes to feel guilty.
Me too.
He said, "Don't teach me any more
meditation, don't teach me."  I said,
"Why do I already feel guilty
because I don't
meditate?"  Do you want
to teach me another meditation now so that I
don’t meditate again?
And
I do this always and everywhere, wherever
you
are, you
meditate.  Someone thinks he is
thinking about a
girl.  He
thinks, what am I, what kind of family did I plant
to meet this girl.
I had a good
day.  I was driving to
work.  Suddenly, I hear Jimi Hendrick playing on the radio
.  I was so
happy.  And suddenly a friend of mine cut me off in his
car
.  And just
think, do your meditation.
Make your creative meditation.
Meditation of the creative voice in your
head.  What seed did I plant for
this stupid fellow to cut me down?
Just think about
it.  Then you go to work,
sleep with your car and forget
about
it.  These are very good one-minute
meditations.
Three times a day, five times a
day.  What time should I
meditate?  Meditate when something
stupid
happens, and meditate when something
good
happens.  I just met the coolest
people in your life.
Mexico
City.  And it was so
cool.  What did I
do [laughter]?  You know, right?
Fine.  These are your
meditation triggers.  Something bad
happened.
or something good
happened.  Then don't say why
I don't say why
I my teacher taught me in different
ways, in strange
ways every day all
day long, everything, everything
.  Made me clean the toilets.
I am the abbot of the monastery.  I can do it, I'm the boss,
I can watch TV whenever I want.
You are not a priest, you cannot
watch TV.  And I was like, "Oh, but,"
he
said, "If there's anything interesting
on TV, I'll
ring the bell."
Bell.  You know, now you
understand why these llamas have such
bells.  This is a bell for the
TV.  When you
hear the bell, run straight down and
go down.  They're showing something interesting on
TV
.  I said, "Yes,
dada."  I started working downstairs so I wouldn't have to
run back and forth.  And I heard a little bell, a
little bell.  Then I run it.
Watch
the news.  Shows news where a
woman's house caught fire
.  She left it on.  Her whole house
burned down.  And she
cries.  Why me?  Why
me?  All people do it.  Why me?  Why did this
happen to me?  Why my house?
Then he says: "Go, go,
why did you send me here
?"  And I said,
"Go,
go."  And I work, work, work.
I continue to work.  Then I hear
the bell again, which is after an hour of descent.
Look, look, there's this
nice
reporter knocking on the door of a poor
man in a very bad part of
New York City.
Knock-knock-knock.  The door where one woman
opens the door and he
says, "You won the lottery."
Here's a check for 5 million dollars
.  They like to show it on
TV.
Screams, dances,
rejoices.  And he
asks me what she didn’t
ask.  Why me?  Why me?  When do you
play the lottery?
Why is no one talking?  Why me
when your house burned down?  Why me?  Why
me?  Why did this happen to me
?  And as far as
the creative hair in your
head is concerned, you will ask, "Why me
all
the time when something bad happens?
That's natural. It's asking why me. But
also when something good
happens, you ask, why me?
By the way, you
[music]
knew, you noticed that I'm not telling you
what to
think? I just want you to ask
yourself this question.
How will you answer the question? That's up
to you. It's your business, it's your
problem. I'm just telling you to
ask this
question. Something good
happens, something bad
happens. Why
me? Then you will answer in your own personal
way.
I don't think this medicine will take
more than dt or 3
minutes, because your life
moves on, it
goes on. Why? You can't sit for 2
hours and think, "Why me, why me,
why
me?  We don't have
time.  I want you to ask this
question for 30
seconds.  You answer this question yourself.   Do
you know your names in yours?  I don't
know them.  Let's get back to
seriousness.  Next picture.
Wait, I know the next
picture.  And the money
ran out.  Now you don't have to
listen carefully to what I tell you.
Why me Why
me the studio gave people started asking,
why me?  Why
me?  Okay, I'll show you the
reading picture.  Let's see how much
time we have.
Okay, we'll take a few breaks from
reading.
You will feel this reading.
Then we will finish this session with
questions and
answers.  Let's read in Tibetan to
get good
luck.  Thief, come here quickly.
Now, now,
[music]
today.  Lento in Spanish.
Just read this.  Don't stay.
Wait, Alda, don't go, don't go.
Okay,
okay.  Tender,
beautiful.
By the way, he himself is the best teacher of
Tibetan.  The best
Tibetan teacher.  Yes.  I give a free lesson
every
week.  How much money will I get
from If you don't come to his classes,
you're crazy.  You are free.  This is
fun.  He knows how to teach
people.  Better than me.  He does it
better than
me.  Don't be crazy about his
activities.
Leave, leave, leave the chair.  Where did you
take
him?  Come back with a chair.  Come back, give us back
our
chair.
Yeah.  Here is the translation.
On the one hand, you have someone
who is
born inside your mother.  But on
the other hand, you
continue the
form that
forces the form.
You continue to exist in that which is
always accepting.  This speaks to the pen,
says
Shala.  If this pen comes from a
pen, from a pen, that's
right, it will never change.
She will never run out of ink in
this
pen.  But if the pen is in use, it will
never run out of ink.
If the pen comes from
me, if the pen comes from my
seeds, and every time I use
his
pen,
I want him to change into someone
else.  Every time you
use
the cloud, the ink runs out.
It's not that the ink
runs out, your
seeds run out to have that
ink.  I don't have any
money anymore.  Where is my bank?
Banker, let's give you another 100 dollars
.  You will explain to my wife why I
spent so much money.
Big question.  A very difficult
question.  When you write with
a pen, you write
something, where does this
writing come from?  Don't talk like that.  Don't
show it like that.  Show it like this.
Raise your hand up.
Music from the cartoon Pink
Panther.  Scripture comes from seeds.
Right.  Very
good.  It's very
difficult.
People
say, "The pen exists on its
own
side."  I ask:
"Why?"  Look, she can write
on
paper herself.  Writing does not come from a pen.
When you move
the pen, your mind makes that writing on the
paper.  Now you have
news.
Why does every minute of the next movie
you see happen in one
direction or another?  Where is this movie going?
I
lived.  I
went to see
some
movie about Wolvarein.  New
movie.  Dead
pool.  By the way, my meditation.
With my meditation system, you can go
to the movies and
meditate.  Why so stupid?
What did I
do?  So who wrote this
movie?  You wrote this
movie every minute.  New picture.  Your
mind is hiding these
pictures.  Don't
forget.  Then things get old.  Why?
Why do
you feel so happy when you finish some films?
I am so happy.  Finally this movie
is over.  I feel like I have to
stay because I paid money
for this goal.  If I don't if I don't like it
when this if I don't
like this movie, I'm I'm glad that
this movie is over.
Why is this happening there?  Because
you have run out of seeds,
they will run out with your body in the same way
.  Your body was created inside your
mother by your workshops.  By the way,
start with the chakras.  Chakras start
first, then channels.  First, chakras are created
, then channels, then everything around
these forms, around these
channels.  Then the flesh inside
it.  6 weeks inside your mother will be enough
.
Each week has its own
chakra, but then you
finish.  What comes from
seeds?  As you use your
body, it ages, right?
If the pen were coming from its
own
side, there is no reason why the
pen should run out of
ink.  I'll say it again
.  If a pen comes from its
own
end, it will
never run out of ink.  If the pen
comes from
you, it will continue to do so all the
time.  But if it comes from your
seeds, they will become old and these
seeds
will die.  Now the
question.  Can we borrow money from someone
?  The board has a lot of money.
I probably spent all this money on
your
children.  In this
book, the
poem is a
discussion, a
struggle between two
people.  There is an angel and there is a devil.
Yes, sometimes in a poem it is an angel who
speaks, sometimes in a poem it is the devil who
speaks.  Who says this is a
$100 rip-off?  And why is there
music from the cartoon Pink Panther
and this piece about how we are born
in our mother's body, she said, the angel
says why?
Because because
life gives up its
own
seeds.  She explains why you are getting old,
angels,
Dana,
why your relationship
ended?  And that's good advice.
I think it should be a $100 angel
.  We'll
do two, and then we'll answer
your
questions.  Would Oscar be willing
to come over?  Oscar is incredible, he
really knows the versions incredibly well.
He is the best, second best
Tibetan reader in this room.
How to do this?  I don't
know.  Can you read
from there?  No.  Yes.
ngang
ля마
Oscarzhe is so modest.
Ready?   I
don't see that he speaks
English.  But I see that it is written that
this will be completely
unrealistic.  And to feel that
thoughts are in the soul and they think that this is
mine.
I'm sorry, it's very difficult for me to see on the
screen what is written here. I know
I'm crazy, explain later.
If things don't come from
seeds, nothing can be mine.
money.  You see, even your mouth cannot
be
yours.  Your nose cannot be your
nose.  But I see your feelings, your
eyes, your whole body, your
stomach, your house, your
things, your wife or husband cannot be
yours.  Your children cannot be
important unless they come from
seeds.  Things that do not come from the
seed.  Things that do not come from seed
cannot be
yours.   There is a
deeper explanation of things.
things that do not happen and the seed
cannot be connected with
others.  Maitri is my son, this is the son of Nur
id.  I will say that you have some
connection with
it, but if there are no
seeds, there can be no connection.
If Maitre comes from his
own side, he cannot
come from his
mother.  If he may come from his own
side, he cannot come from
his mother.
[music]
Only those things that come from
seeds can come
to pass.  If
the handle comes from its own
side, I can never
have it, because it does not come from
my
seeds.  The connection with this pen also
comes from my family.
And when I use this connection, these are
my
seeds too.  If a thing does not happen, the seed will
never grow
.  If things do not come from
seeds, no one can
have them.  Think about it.   A
world
that does not come from seeds is
impossible.  A pen that does not come
from a seed never has, never
runs out of
ink.  You can't buy a pen that
doesn't come from a
seed.  Sometimes you need a pen and
your friend gives you this pen.
Sometimes you need a pen, go to the store and
buy it.  And they are told: "We are
out of all the
pens. You don't get pens from
the store, you get pens from
seeds."  You need to share the things
you have
.  Then you will have even
more.  Jesus said this several times.
Jesus, the great master of
seeds.  He talks about seeds all the
time.  What you want, give to
someone else.  Someone asked
you if she stole your
sweater.  Take his phone number and
call, ask: "Do you need my coat
?"
Someone hit you on one
side.  Ah, hit this side.  This is
also a good
side.  Master Seed
talks like this.  So, are you ready?  Are you
ready,
Rock?  We have enough gas
to get home.
OK.  We have a credit card.
Who wrote
this?  I know the right answer
is
you.  Is it an angel or a devil speaking here?
Here in this
verse.  And why?
Don't answer a question you want to
get money from with a
question.  You must answer
confidently.  It must be the angels
speaking.  Why?
Because it comes from
my picture, the one with the tree,
the woman with the tree, remember, with the
plant.  The very first picture.
Seeds.
Seeds.  If they say seeds, they
must be
what?  This is an angel.
The devil doesn't like to talk about
seeds.  Fine.
So, the
last thing.
Utima has been found.  One last time.
It would be great if Gibson
came
here now.  Cool
translator, incredible
translator.  I don't know what he's doing here
[music]
Syria.  I'm very happy that he is here.
I would like to also invite
welcome, wish his partner
[music]
Emily.
What we
call a pocket book of darma is gypsonized.
He has already finished the
door.  They are approximately 600 years old.  They are 600 years old.
The idea is to have a
small book that you can
carry either in your pocket or in your
purse.  Translation
from Word or here's Tim.
They are really cool if you have Torah or a
fight with your
husband.  They are very heavy, big,
heavy, big
books.  I'll give you this on the
head now.  But Gibna's specialty is
small books.
We call them pocket books or
bag books.  He is starting his third
book soon.  Very, very
soon.
So, let's begin.   For
many, many years he helped
the team that helped Guadalajara, the
Guadalajara team.  Associated with emigrants
who came from South America and
tried to cross into Central America.   a
special house where they
rest.  People
can
shower, they can relax, eat
these
grants.  Then they board the train
and continue on their way
.  They have been helping this project for
more than years.
I won't ask about this
picture.  These are people from
Taiwan.  The team in Taiwan gives them these
boxes.  They put their coins in this
box.
And so we collected a lot, a lot,
a lot
[music]
we also, they also support
the team that translates these books, the
translation of these books is titled.
more than you It is
written here in English that people are being held by the
hand because
nothing.  Ali will read in
Spanish now, and we will talk about
it later.  We are in the negative, we have 2
minutes.  Will save my bank account.
Two people by the hands, because nothing.
Teach them not to think about anything
.  Make them
concentrate.  Busy with business every
time they meditate
and make them a master of
meditation.  I don't see any further. Let me
explain to you.  Said he wanted.
If you
join, if you become an AC teacher
in Latin
America, say Aldo
Aldo.  And you can talk like this
.  What will you do in Costa Rica?
What will you
teach?  Oh, we will take people by the
hand, we will lead them to nothing
.
Then we will teach them a special
meditation.  Don't think about anything.
Then we will
teach them when they
meditate.  Think about as big
things as possible.  We will make real
meditators.  Who's
speaking?  Who's speaking?
Kiri, Kiri.
And Kiri is Alisha's son.  Aisha Anatolia.
This is the devil.  He said.
Cha
[music]
for loving very tasty things.   In
Russian, this is brushwood.  Hot brushwood.
When last year's
stories were going on, he really wanted to be churlish and we
did it.  I wish.  People say to him, "Have
n't you been to Mexico for so long?
Why did you come back?" They
ask. Because I
remember when I went to see the
big
cathedral, next to this cathedral there was
Churio. And that day I became very
religious.
I always want to go to that
cathedral now, because they sell this
dessert there. In Russian it reminds me of a
city. Churio is called in English and
pon. And this boy gave him this
bag, because he
loves it.